Tracy Early papers, Inclusive: 1924-2005, Bulk: circa 1940-2005
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- Personal Materials, 1948-2005; 2
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1991-1992 (Box 103, Folder 11)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1992-1993 (Box 103, Folder 12)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1994 (Box 103, Folder 13)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1995 (Box 103, Folder 14)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1996 (Box 103, Folder 15)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1997-2003, 2005 (Box 103, Folder 16)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, undated (Box 103, Folder 17)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Grady Gaston Early, 1954, 1962, undated (Box 103, Folder 18)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Andrea Nicole Early to Tracy, 1989-1993, undated (Box 103, Folder 19)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Worley Early to Tracy, 1951-1952, 1954-1959, undated (Box 103, Folder 20)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Granny Early to Tracy, 1955-1956, undated (Box 103, Folder 21)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Granny Early, 1954-1960, 1962 (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Mrs. I.H. Walton to Tracy, 1953-1954, 1957, 1964, 1966-1967, 1970, undated (Box 104, Folder 2)
  - Personal Correspondence: Francis L. Walton and Bobby Ray Hudson to Tracy, 1953 (Box 104, Folder 3)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Mrs. R. J. Derby to Tracy, undated (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Aunt to Worley Early, 1955, 1957-1958 (Box 104, Folder 5)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Aunt to Worley Early, 1958-1959, undated (Box 104, Folder 6)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Aunt to Lillian Early, 1959, 1975 (Box 104, Folder 7)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Grady Gaston Early to Tracy, 1953-1956 (Box 104, Folder 8)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Grady Gaston Early to Tracy, 1957-1958, 1960, 1962-1963 (Box 104, Folder 9)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Grady Gaston Early to Tracy, 1963-1965 (Box 104, Folder 10)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Grady Gaston Early to Tracy, 1965-1967 (Box 104, Folder 11)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Grady Gaston Early to Tracy, 1968-1970 (Box 104, Folder 12)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Grady Gaston Early to Tracy, 1970-1971 (Box 104, Folder 13)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Grady Gaston Early to Tracy, 1971-1972 (Box 104, Folder 14)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Grady Gaston Early to Tracy, 1972-1974 (Box 104, Folder 15)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Grady Gaston Early to Tracy, 1974-1978 (Box 104, Folder 16)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Grady Gaston Early to Tracy, 1978-1980 (Box 104, Folder 17)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Grady Gaston Early to Tracy, 1980-1982 (Box 104, Folder 18)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Grady Gaston Early to Tracy, 1982-1983 (Box 104, Folder 19)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Grady Gaston Early to Tracy, 1984-1986 (Box 104, Folder 20)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Gaston Grady Early to Tracy, 1987-1989 (Box 104, Folder 21)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Grady Gaston Early to Tracy, 1989-1990, 1992 (Box 104, Folder 22)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Grady Gaston Early to Tracy, 1992-1996 (Box 105, Folder 1)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Grady Gaston Early to Tracy, 1997-1998, 2000-2002 (Box 105, Folder 2)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Grady Gaston Early to Tracy, 2004-2005, undated (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - Personal Correspondence: To and from Tracy and Linda Britton, 1955 (Box 105, Folder 4)
  - Personal Correspondence: To and from Tracy and Linda Britton, 1955-1959, 1997, 2000 (Box 105, Folder 5)
  - Personal Correspondence: To and from Tracy and Linda Britton, 2000, undated (Box 105, Folder 6)
  - Awards, Certificates, and Diplomas, 1950, 1952, 1954, 1956-1958 (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - Awards, Certificates, and Diplomas, 1963, 1974, 1982, 1991, 1997 (Box 105, Folder 8)
  - Planners, 1984-2005 (Box 105, Folder 9)
  - Scrapbook: (1 of 3), circa 1940s (Box 105, Folder 10)
  - Scrapbook: (2 of 3), circa 1940s (Box 105, Folder 11)
  - Scrapbook: (3 of 3), circa 1940s (Box 105, Folder 12)
  - Scrapbook: (1 of 3), 1964-1968 (Box 105, Folder 13)
  - Scrapbook: (2 of 3), 1964-1968 (Box 105, Folder 14)
  - Scrapbook: (3 of 3), 1964-1968 (Box 105, Folder 15)
- Subjects, 1924-2007; 3
  This series contains all files that Tracy Early organized by subject. Included in this series are newspaper articles and clippings, materials pertaining to committees and associations he was on, schools he attended, churches he worked for, and information regarding his book Sidebars.
  - Newspapers: General, 1961-2000 (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - Newspapers: Africa, 1987-1991 (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - Newspapers: Africa, 1992-1997 (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - Newspapers: Baptist General Association of Virginia, 1967 (Box 106, Folder 4)
  - Newspapers: Baptists, 1952-1962, undated (Box 106, Folder 5)
  - Newspapers: Billy Graham, 1966-1969 June 8 (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - Newspapers: Billy Graham, 1969 June 10-14 (Box 106, Folder 7)
  - Newspapers: Billy Graham, 1969 June 15-21 (Box 106, Folder 8)
  - Newspapers: Billy Graham, 1969 June 22-August (Box 106, Folder 9)
  - Newspapers: Billy Graham, 1970 May-June (Box 106, Folder 10)
  - Newspapers: Billy Graham, 1970 August-1983 (Box 106, Folder 11)
  - Newspapers: Billy Graham, undated (Box 106, Folder 12)
  - Newspapers: Biographical Sketches, 1978-1984 (Box 106, Folder 13)
  - Newspapers: Biographical Sketches, 1984-1987, undated (Box 106, Folder 14)
  - Newspapers: Church and State, 1984 March 8 (Box 106, Folder 15)
  - Newspapers: Church Center for the United Nations, 1968-1969 September (Box 106, Folder 16)
  - Newspapers: Church Center for the United Nations, 1969 November (Box 106, Folder 17)
  - Newspapers: Church Center for the United Nations, 1970-1971 (Box 106, Folder 18)
  - Newspapers: Church Center for the United Nations, 1972-1973 January (Box 106, Folder 19)
  - Newspapers: Church Center for the United Nations: (1 of 2), 1973 March (Box 106, Folder 20)
  - Newspapers: Church Center for the United Nations: (2 of 2), 1973 March (Box 106, Folder 21)
  - Newspapers: Church Center for the United Nations, 1973 April-June 19 (Box 106, Folder 22)
  - Newspapers: Church Center for the United Nations, 1973 June 22-July (Box 106, Folder 23)
  - Newspapers: Church Center for the United Nations, 1976-1977 (Box 106, Folder 24)
  - Newspapers: Church Center for the United Nations, 1997 (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - Newspapers: Church Center for the United Nations, 2003 May-October (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - Newspapers: Church Center for the United Nations: (1 of 4), undated (Box 107, Folder 3)
  - Newspapers: Church Center for the United Nations: (2 of 4), undated (Box 107, Folder 4)
  - Newspapers: Church Center for the United Nations: (3 of 4), undated (Box 107, Folder 5)
  - Newspapers: Church Center for the United Nations: (4 of 4), undated (Box 107, Folder 6)
  - Newspapers: Church of Scientology, 1977-1983 (Box 107, Folder 7)
  - Newspapers: Clive Barnes, 1970-1971 May 19 (Box 107, Folder 8)
  - Newspapers: Clive Barnes, 1971 May 23-September (Box 107, Folder 9)
  - Newspapers: Clive Barnes, 1971 October-November 5 (Box 107, Folder 10)
  - Newspapers: Clive Barnes, 1971 November 17-December 13 (Box 107, Folder 11)
  - Newspapers: Clive Barnes, 1971 December 26-1974 (Box 107, Folder 12)
  - Newspapers: Crime, 1968-1969 September (Box 107, Folder 13)
  - Newspapers: Crime, 1969 November-1970 October 15 (Box 107, Folder 14)
  - Newspapers: Crime, 1970 October 17-November 12 (Box 107, Folder 15)
  - Newspapers: Crime, 1970 November 15-1971 April 22 (Box 107, Folder 16)
  - Newspapers: Crime, 1971 April 25-September 4 (Box 107, Folder 17)
  - Newspapers: Crime, 1971 September 8-1972 March (Box 107, Folder 18)
  - Newspapers: Crime, 1972 April-1973 April 15 (Box 107, Folder 19)
  - Newspapers: Crime, 1973 April 27-1975 March 17 (Box 107, Folder 20)
  - Newspapers: Crime, 1975 August-1978 February (Box 107, Folder 21)
  - Newspapers: Crime, 1978 June-1992 (Box 107, Folder 22)
  - Newspapers: Cults, 1983-1984 January (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - Newspapers: Cults, 1984 February-1986 (Box 108, Folder 2)
  - Newspapers: Dysautonomia, 1956-1971 (Box 108, Folder 3)
  - Newspapers: Dysautonomia, 1972 January-May (Box 108, Folder 4)
  - Newspapers: Dysautonomia, 1972 August-1973 January (Box 108, Folder 5)
  - Newspapers: Dysautonomia, 1973 March-1974, undated (Box 108, Folder 6)
  - Newspapers: East Germany, 1968 (Box 108, Folder 7)
  - Newspapers: East Germany, 1969 (Box 108, Folder 8)
  - Newspapers: East Germany, 1970 (Box 108, Folder 9)
  - Newspapers: Easter, 1969 (Box 108, Folder 10)
  - Newspapers: Easter, 1970 (Box 108, Folder 11)
  - Newspapers: Easter, 1971 April (Box 108, Folder 12)
  - Newspapers: Easter, 1971 September (Box 108, Folder 13)
  - Newspapers: Easter, 1972-1974 (Box 108, Folder 14)
  - Newspapers: Edward M. Egan, 2000-2002, undated (Box 108, Folder 15)
  - Newspapers: Ernest Lefever, 1980-1981 May 20 (Box 108, Folder 16)
  - Newspapers: Ernest Lefever, 1981 May 22-1983 (Box 108, Folder 17)
  - Newspapers: Federal Bureau of Investigation, 2001 (Box 108, Folder 18)
  - Newspapers: Frances L. Loeb, 1971-1983 (Box 108, Folder 19)
  - Newspapers: Future Articles, 1972 May 1, undated (Box 108, Folder 20)
  - Newspapers: General Board of Global Ministries, 1982 (Box 108, Folder 21)
  - Newspapers: General Board of Global Ministries, 1991-1992 (Box 108, Folder 22)
  - Newspapers: General Board of Global Ministries, 1994, undated (Box 108, Folder 23)
  - Newspapers: George McGovern, 1971 February-May 2 (Box 109, Folder 1)
  - Newspapers: George McGovern, 1971 May 10-June 9 (Box 109, Folder 2)
  - Newspapers: George McGovern, 1971 June 10-July 15 (Box 109, Folder 3)
  - Newspapers: George McGovern, 1971 July 17-24 (Box 109, Folder 4)
  - Newspapers: George McGovern, 1971 July 29-September 14 (Box 109, Folder 5)
  - Newspapers: George McGovern, 1971 September 20-November 11 (Box 109, Folder 6)
  - Newspapers: George McGovern, 1971 November 21-1972 May (Box 109, Folder 7)
  - Newspapers: George McGovern, 1972 June-July 13 (Box 109, Folder 8)
  - Newspapers: George McGovern, 1972 July 13-August 11 (Box 109, Folder 9)
  - Newspapers: George McGovern, 1972 August 13-October 6 (Box 109, Folder 10)
  - Newspapers: George McGovern, 1972 October 8-1984 (Box 109, Folder 11)
  - Newspapers: Greek Americans, 1971 (Box 109, Folder 12)
  - Newspapers: Greek Americans, 1972 January-February 3 (Box 109, Folder 13)
  - Newspapers: Greek Americans, 1972 February 5-July (Box 109, Folder 14)
  - Newspapers: Greek Americans, undated (Box 109, Folder 15)
  - Newspapers: Institute on Religion and Democracy, 1981 May-October (Box 109, Folder 16)
  - Newspapers: Institute on Religion and Democracy, 1981 November-1982 May (Box 109, Folder 17)
  - Newspapers: Institute on Religion and Democracy, 1982 August (Box 109, Folder 18)
  - Newspapers: Institute on Religion and Democracy, 1983 January 17 (Box 109, Folder 19)
  - Newspapers: Institute on Religion and Democracy, 1983 January 23-25 (Box 109, Folder 20)
  - Newspapers: Institute on Religion and Democracy, 1983 January 26-June (Box 109, Folder 21)
  - Newspapers: Institute on Religion and Democracy, 1983 October-1984, undated (Box 109, Folder 22)
  - Newspapers: James Forman, 1964-1969 May 7 (Box 110, Folder 1)
  - Newspapers: James Forman, 1969 May 8-25 (Box 110, Folder 2)
  - Newspapers: James Forman, 1969 May 25-June 11 (Box 110, Folder 3)
  - Newspapers: James Forman, 1969 June 12-20 (Box 110, Folder 4)
  - Newspapers: James Forman, 1969 June 22-July 3 (Box 110, Folder 5)
  - Newspapers: James Forman, 1969 July 5-20 (Box 110, Folder 6)
  - Newspapers: James Forman, 1969 July 21-August 22 (Box 110, Folder 7)
  - Newspapers: James Forman, 1969 August 30-1970 June (Box 110, Folder 8)
  - Newspapers: James Forman, 1970 July-2005, undated (Box 110, Folder 9)
  - Newspapers: Jews: School Aid, 1971 August (Box 110, Folder 10)
  - Newspapers: Jimmy Carter, 1976 May-June (Box 110, Folder 11)
  - Newspapers: Jimmy Carter, 1976 July (Box 110, Folder 12)
  - Newspapers: Jimmy Carter, 1976 August 3-16 (Box 110, Folder 13)
  - Newspapers: Jimmy Carter, 1976 August 16-September 20 (Box 110, Folder 14)
  - Newspapers: Jimmy Carter, 1976 September 25-October (Box 110, Folder 15)
  - Newspapers: Jimmy Carter, 1976 November-1977 January (Box 110, Folder 16)
  - Newspapers: Jimmy Carter, 1977 May-1980 April (Box 110, Folder 17)
  - Newspapers: Jimmy Carter, 1980 July-1981 July (Box 110, Folder 18)
  - Newspapers: Jimmy Carter, 1981 August-1986 (Box 110, Folder 19)
  - Newspapers: John C. Bennett, 1964-1970 May 8 (Box 111, Folder 1)
  - Newspapers: John C. Bennett, 1970 May 10 (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - Newspapers: John C. Bennett, 1970 May 14 (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - Newspapers: John C. Bennett, 1970 May 15-19 (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - Newspapers: John C. Bennett, 1971 (Box 111, Folder 5)
  - Newspapers: John C. Bennett, 1986, undated (Box 111, Folder 6)
  - Newspapers: John Lindsay, 1970-1971 March 12 (Box 111, Folder 7)
  - Newspapers: John Lindsay, 1971 March 13-April 8 (Box 111, Folder 8)
  - Newspapers: John Lindsay, 1971 April 13-28 (Box 111, Folder 9)
  - Newspapers: John Lindsay, 1971 May (Box 111, Folder 10)
  - Newspapers: John Lindsay, 1971 June-July 14 (Box 111, Folder 11)
  - Newspapers: John Lindsay, 1971 July 22 (Box 111, Folder 12)
  - Newspapers: John Lindsay, 1971 July 22-August 12 (Box 111, Folder 13)
  - Newspapers: John Lindsay, 1971 August 12-September 6 (Box 111, Folder 14)
  - Newspapers: John Lindsay, 1971 September 10-October 16 (Box 111, Folder 15)
  - Newspapers: John Lindsay, 1971 October 25-December (Box 111, Folder 16)
  - Newspapers: John Lindsay, 1972-1973 (Box 111, Folder 17)
  - Newspapers: John O’Connor, 1984-1985 March 17 (Box 111, Folder 18)
  - Newspapers: John O’Connor, 1985 March 18-1986 March (Box 111, Folder 19)
  - Newspapers: John O’Connor, 1986 June 4 (Box 111, Folder 20)
  - Newspapers: John O’Connor, 1986 September-1989 March (Box 111, Folder 21)
  - Newspapers: John O’Connor, 1989 May-1990 June 14 (Box 112, Folder 1)
  - Newspapers: John O’Connor, 1990 June 17-1991 October (Box 112, Folder 2)
  - Newspapers: John O’Connor, 1991 November-1995 (Box 112, Folder 3)
  - Newspapers: John O’Connor, 1999-2000 January 3 (Box 112, Folder 4)
  - Newspapers: John O’Connor, 2000 January 13-May 11 (Box 112, Folder 5)
  - Newspapers: John O’Connor, 2000 May 11, undated (Box 112, Folder 6)
  - Newspapers: Junk Faxes, 2000-2001 October 5 (Box 112, Folder 7)
  - Newspapers: Junk Faxes, 2001 October 18-2003 July (Box 112, Folder 8)
  - Newspapers: Junk Faxes, 2003 December-2004 May (Box 112, Folder 9)
  - Newspapers: Junk Faxes, 2004 June (Box 112, Folder 10)
  - Newspapers: Junk Faxes, 2004 July (Box 112, Folder 11)
  - Newspapers: Matthew Troy, 1969-1970 February (Box 112, Folder 12)
  - Newspapers: Matthew Troy, 1970 March (Box 112, Folder 13)
  - Newspapers: Matthew Troy, 1970 April-October (Box 112, Folder 14)
  - Newspapers: Matthew Troy, 1971 January-October (Box 112, Folder 15)
  - Newspapers: Matthew Troy, 1971 November-1980 (Box 112, Folder 16)
  - Newspapers: Matthew Troy: Endorsement of George McGovern, 1971 (Box 112, Folder 17)
  - Newspapers: Mayoral Election: New York City, 1969 June 19 (Box 112, Folder 18)
  - Newspapers: Mayoral Election: New York City, 1969 June 19-August 8 (Box 112, Folder 19)
  - Newspapers: Mayoral Election: New York City, 1969 August 14 (Box 112, Folder 20)
  - Newspapers: Mayoral Election: New York City, 1969 August 19-November 4 (Box 112, Folder 21)
  - Newspapers: Mayoral Election: New York City: (1 of 2), 1969 November 5 (Box 112, Folder 22)
  - Newspapers: Mayoral Election: New York City: (2 of 2), 1969 November 5 (Box 113, Folder 1)
  - Newspapers: Mayoral Election: New York City, 1969 November 29-December (Box 113, Folder 2)
  - Newspapers: Mayoral Election: New York City, 1973 February-September (Box 113, Folder 3)
  - Newspapers: Mayoral Election: New York City, undated (Box 113, Folder 4)
  - Newspapers: Ministry in the South, 1963-1966 (Box 113, Folder 5)
  - Newspapers: Ministry in the South, 1967-1969 January 16 (Box 113, Folder 6)
  - Newspapers: Ministry in the South, 1969 January 30-June 19 (Box 113, Folder 7)
  - Newspapers: Ministry in the South: (1 of 4), undated (Box 113, Folder 8)
  - Newspapers: Ministry in the South: (2 of 4), undated (Box 113, Folder 9)
  - Newspapers: Ministry in the South: (3 of 4), undated (Box 113, Folder 10)
  - Newspapers: Ministry in the South: (4 of 4), undated (Box 113, Folder 11)
  - Newspapers: New York City: Catholics, 1982 (Box 113, Folder 12)
  - Newspapers: New York City: Churches: Crimes, 1969-1971 January (Box 113, Folder 13)
  - Newspapers: New York City: Churches: Crimes, 1971 February-March 12 (Box 113, Folder 14)
  - Newspapers: New York City: Churches: Crimes, 1971 March 12-31 (Box 113, Folder 15)
  - Newspapers: New York City: Churches: Crimes, 1971 May-July 15 (Box 113, Folder 16)
  - Newspapers: New York City: Churches: Crimes, 1971 July 29-August (Box 113, Folder 17)
  - Newspapers: New York City: Churches: Crimes, 1971 September-1986, undated (Box 113, Folder 18)
  - Newspapers: New York City: Churches: General, 1967-1969 March 23 (Box 113, Folder 19)
  - Newspapers: New York City: Churches: General, 1969 March 28-October (Box 113, Folder 20)
  - Newspapers: New York City: Churches: General, 1969 November-1970 January (Box 113, Folder 21)
  - Newspapers: New York City: Churches: General, 1970 February (Box 113, Folder 22)
  - Newspapers: New York City: Churches: General, 1970 May-June 13 (Box 114, Folder 1)
  - Newspapers: New York City: Churches: General, 1970 June 14-October (Box 114, Folder 2)
  - Newspapers: New York City: Churches: General, 1970 November-December 6 (Box 114, Folder 3)
  - Newspapers: New York City: Churches: General, 1970 December 13-1971 February (Box 114, Folder 4)
  - Newspapers: New York City: Churches: General, 1971 March-May 10 (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - Newspapers: New York City: Churches: General, 1971 May 23-July (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - Newspapers: New York City: Churches: General, 1971 September-1972 March 5 (Box 114, Folder 7)
  - Newspapers: New York City: Churches: General, 1972 March 12-October (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - Newspapers: New York City: Churches: General, 1972 December-1973 March (Box 114, Folder 9)
  - Newspapers: New York City: Churches: General, 1973 April-1974 May 12 (Box 114, Folder 10)
  - Newspapers: New York City: Churches: General, 1974 May 19-November (Box 114, Folder 11)
  - Newspapers: New York City: Churches: General, 1975 (Box 114, Folder 12)
  - Newspapers: New York City: Churches: General, 1976 (Box 114, Folder 13)
  - Newspapers: New York City: Churches: General, 1981 January-March 1 (Box 114, Folder 14)
  - Newspapers: New York City: Churches: General, 1981 March 2-May 17 (Box 114, Folder 15)
  - Newspapers: New York City: Churches: General, 1981 May 24-December (Box 114, Folder 16)
  - Newspapers: New York City: Churches: General, 1982 January-April 4 (Box 114, Folder 17)
  - Newspapers: New York City: Churches: General, 1982 April 4-1983 January 16 (Box 114, Folder 18)
  - Newspapers: New York City: Churches: General, 1983 April-1984 (Box 114, Folder 19)
  - Newspapers: New York City: Churches: General, 1985-1991 (Box 114, Folder 20)
  - Newspapers: New York City: Churches: General, undated (Box 114, Folder 21)
  - Newspapers: Orthodox Church, 1970-1971 January (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - Newspapers: Orthodox Church, 1971 March-July 8 (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - Newspapers: Orthodox Church, 1971 July 16-September 9 (Box 115, Folder 3)
  - Newspapers: Orthodox Church, 1971 September 12-December (Box 115, Folder 4)
  - Newspapers: Orthodox Church, 1974, undated (Box 115, Folder 5)
  - Newspapers: Police Corruption, 1971 July-August 7 (Box 115, Folder 6)
  - Newspapers: Police Corruption, 1971 August 13-31 (Box 115, Folder 7)
  - Subjects: Newspapers: Police Corruption, 1971 September 1-6 (Box 115, Folder 8)
  - Newspapers: Police Corruption, 1971 September 7-1972 January (Box 115, Folder 9)
  - Newspapers: Presbyterian Health, Education, and Welfare Association, 1976-1982 (Box 115, Folder 10)
  - Newspapers: Presbyterian Health, Education, and Welfare Association, 1983-1985 (Box 115, Folder 11)
  - Newspapers: Presbyterian Health, Education, and Welfare Association, 1987, undated (Box 115, Folder 12)
  - Newspapers: Presbyterians: (1 of 2), 1984 January 12 (Box 115, Folder 13)
  - Newspapers: Presbyterians: (2 of 2), 1984 January 12 (Box 115, Folder 14)
  - Newspapers: Presbyterians, circa 1984 (Box 115, Folder 15)
  - Newspapers: Presbyterians, 1985 February (Box 115, Folder 16)
  - Newspapers: Presbyterians, 1985 November (Box 115, Folder 17)
  - Newspapers: Presbyterians, 1987 August (Box 115, Folder 18)
  - Newspapers: Presbyterians, 1988 September 8, undated (Box 115, Folder 19)
  - Newspapers: Presidential Election of 1872 and 1972 (Box 115, Folder 20)
  - Newspapers: Presidential Election of 1968, 1968 September 18-22 (Box 115, Folder 21)
  - Newspapers: Presidential Election of 1968, 1968 September 26-October 24 (Box 115, Folder 22)
  - Newspapers: Presidential Election of 1968, 1968 October 27-November 4 (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - Newspapers: Presidential Election of 1968, 1968 November 4-26 (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - Newspapers: Presidential Election of 1968, 1969 January 10 (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Newspapers: Presidential Election of 1968, 1969 January 15 (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - Newspapers: Presidential Election of 1976, 1975-1976 January 18 (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - Newspapers: Presidential Election of 1976, 1976 January 22-March 10 (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - Newspapers: Presidential Election of 1976, 1976 March 13-24 (Box 116, Folder 7)
  - Newspapers: Presidential Election of 1976, 1976 April (Box 116, Folder 8)
  - Newspapers: Presidential Election of 1976, 1976 May 1-11 (Box 116, Folder 9)
  - Newspapers: Presidential Election of 1976, 1976 May 12-31 (Box 116, Folder 10)
  - Newspapers: Presidential Election of 1976, 1976 June-July 23 (Box 116, Folder 11)
  - Newspapers: Presidential Election of 1976, 1976 July 25-August (Box 116, Folder 12)
  - Newspapers: Presidential Election of 1976, 1976 October-November 1 (Box 116, Folder 13)
  - Newspapers: Presidential Election of 1976, 1976 November 3-1979 (Box 116, Folder 14)
  - Newspapers: Presidential Election of 1980, 1979-1980 February (Box 116, Folder 15)
  - Newspapers: Presidential Election of 1980, 1980 March (Box 116, Folder 16)
  - Newspapers: Presidential Election of 1980, 1980 April-July (Box 116, Folder 17)
  - Newspapers: Presidential Election of 1980, 1980 August-November 5 (Box 116, Folder 18)
  - Newspapers: Presidential Election of 1980, 1980 November 5-1981 (Box 116, Folder 19)
  - Newspapers: Presidential Election of 1984, 1984 February-August 21 (Box 116, Folder 20)
  - Newspapers: Presidential Election of 1984, 1984 August 24-November (Box 116, Folder 21)
  - Newspapers: Publication Attempts: Tracy Early: (1 of 8), 1971-1972 (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - Newspapers: Publication Attempts: Tracy Early: (2 of 8), 1971-1972 (Box 117, Folder 2)
  - Newspapers: Publication Attempts: Tracy Early: (3 of 8), 1971-1972 (Box 117, Folder 3)
  - Newspapers: Publication Attempts: Tracy Early: (4 of 8), 1971-1972 (Box 117, Folder 4)
  - Newspapers: Publication Attempts: Tracy Early: (5 of 8), 1971-1972 (Box 117, Folder 5)
  - Newspapers: Publication Attempts: Tracy Early: (6 of 8), 1971-1972 (Box 117, Folder 6)
  - Newspapers: Publication Attempts: Tracy Early: (7 of 8), 1971-1972 (Box 117, Folder 7)